[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "apple",
        "back":"яблоко",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "orange",
        "back":"апельсин",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "cat",
        "back":"кот",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "dog",
        "back":"собака",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "living room",
        "back":"зал",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "bed",
        "back":"спальня",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "tomato",
        "back":"помидор",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "potato",
        "back":"картофель",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "carrot",
        "back":"морковь",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "ball",
        "back":"мяч",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "doll",
        "back":"кукла",
        "setName":"English"
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "t",
        "back":"ссылка",
        "setName":"tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "img",
        "back":"изображение",
        "setName":"tags"
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "border",
        "back":"рамка",
        "setName":"css"
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "background",
        "back":"фон",
        "setName":"css"
    }


]